

Hobbies

I spend my free time reading books, doing sports, climbing and watching movies and series

About Me

I'm Bahram Basdak, a React developer experienced in creating frontend applications using React, JavaScript, HTML, and CSS. With over 3 years of expertise in designing and developing front-end web solutions, I focus on crafting user-friendly interfaces and solving complex problems collaboratively to achieve team objectives.

Educations

Masters Electronics engineering Shahid Sattari Aeronautical University

Jul 2008 - Jul 2012

Description:

Bachelor's project of the main program of flight simulators

Smart home system programming

Employment History

▶ Front-end Developer (React-Next.js)

Teamyab

Oct 2022 - Aug 2023

Description:

Programming the front end of the company site

fix bugs

Software testing

Software expert

Petro Ahoura

Apr 2020 - Oct 2022

Description:

I was working as a software developer, user interface designer and electronic circuit designer for the company

Courses

Jump Frontend with React

Guera

Jul 2022 - Sep 2022

JavaScript

freecodecamp

Feb 2022 - Jun 2022

Responsive Web Design

freecodecamp

Dec 2021 - Feb 2022

Projects

www.teamyab.com for Teamyab

Oct 2022 - Jul 2023

Description:

As my main project I worked on the Teamyab in collaboration with Teamyab's team

Project Link:

https://teamyab.com/

Social Links

Website https://bahrambasdak.netlify.app/

Linkedin
https://www.linkedin.com/in/bahrambasd
ak/

Github https://github.com/bahrambasdak

▶ Huralya(web3) for ponisha.ir

May 2022 - Jul 2022

Description:

The front-end project of a website in the blockchain field with features such as connecting to Trustvallet and Metamask

Project Link:

https://huralya-web3.netlify.app/

Product Manager for Quera

Feb 2022 - Mar 2022

Description:

Project management panel of a store with the capabilities of managing, removing and adding products

Project Link:

https://bahrambasdak.netlify.app/

▶ Face Landmark

Jul 2022 - Aug 2022

Description:

A project with the ability to recognize the human face and draw points according to the shape of that face

Project Link:

https://face-landmark.netlify.app